freemoneysystem.net 2015-05-28

# Privacy

* * *

Privacy Policy Statement - 'FreeMoneySystem'

Note on translation - This Privacy Policy Statement may have been translated into various languages for the convenience of 'FreeMoneySystem' Users. While the translation is correct to the best of 'FreeMoneySystem's' knowledge, 'FreeMoneySystem' is not responsible or liable in the event of an inaccuracy. English is the controlling language of this Privacy Policy Statement, and any translation has been prepared for you as a courtesy only. In the event of a conflict between the English-language version of this Privacy Policy Statement and a version that has been translated into another language, the English-language version shall control.

Important - This Privacy Policy Statement outlines the use of all identifying personal information submitted and collected on http://www.FreeMoneySystem.co/ (the "Site"). This privacy notice does not encompass other websites or third-party links referenced to or by 'FreeMoneySystem' in any way, including but no limited to print, online, or in e-mail. 'FreeMoneySystem', its affiliates, clients and all of their respective authorized representatives, officers, directors, employees, agents, shareholders, licensors, attorneys, successors, and assigns ("FreeMoneySystem"), is firmly committed to protecting personal and financial information. This Privacy Policy statement embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices.

1.       Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms

'FreeMoneySystem' is committed to protecting its users' privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our Site. By accessing our Site, you acknowledge and fully understand the Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Site Privacy Policy Statement.

2.       Information we collect and how we use it

When you use or connect to our Site through your computer or a mobile device, the owners and publishers of the Site collect certain information from and about its users in a few ways, directly from our web server logs, from you, with the aid of cookies, with web beacons, and through the use of website analytics through a third party service provider. We may collect personally identifiable information necessary for internal marketing purposes based on user activity, registration and billing from customers who purchase our products and services online.

'FreeMoneySystem's proxy is a gateway for the user's network, and is set for the purposes of retrieving such information, and base marketing material on it. We do not collect any sensitive information.

Visitors to our Site can register to create an account, access the Site, download Software, and possibly purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as your name, address, e-mail, telephone number or facsimile number, location, account number and other relevant information. We also collect your IP computer address. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

3.       Web server logs

When you visit our Site, we may track information through web server logs to better administer the Site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include but is not limited to your Internet Protocol address ("IP"), the type of browser or computer you use, the number of links you click within the Site, the geographical location from which you accessed the Site, the date and time of your visit, the name of your Internet service provider, any web pages you linked to our Site from, and pages you viewed on the Site.

4.       Use of cookies

'FreeMoneySystem' may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server to identify that specific user the next time he or she visits the website. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

We do not allow other companies on our Site to place cookies, unless there is a temporary overriding of a part in the Site (such as integrating another site that relies on third-party cookies, into the existing website).

5.       Modifying cookie settings

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to delete or decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Site.

6.       Use of web beacons or gif files

This Site may contain electronic images known as "Web Beacons" (also called single-pixel gifs) that allow the owners and publishers of the Site to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver similar services. The owners and publishers of the Site may include Web Beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some Web Beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or e-mail communications. These Web Beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer, for the benefit of 'FreeMoneySystem'. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or e-mails and compiles anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and e-mails bring you to our website and how you use the Site. 'FreeMoneySystem's' Web Beacons are not used to collect or access your identifying personal information.

7.       Notice on Disclosure of user personal information

'FreeMoneySystem' reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, sites and affiliates, including brokers, to help enhance its service offerings, but does not sell or forward identifying personal information to third party companies. Personal User information collected by or submitted to 'FreeMoneySystem' shall not be disclosed to any third parties without your permission, unless such information: (i) to fulfill your service requests; (ii) is required to be disclosed by law, regulation, legal process, law enforcement or government regulatory authorities, in which case we shall give you as much advance notice as is reasonably practicable in order to allow you to limit or restrict to such disclosure; or (iii) is required to be disclosed in order for us to protect our legal rights or defend against liability; or (iv) in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of 'FreeMoneySystem'.

8.       Opting out

If you wish, you may choose not to receive emails, newsletters or other communications from the 'FreeMoneySystem' by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in the email communication sent to your registered email account with the Site.

9.       Accessing and changing personal information

You can ensure that your identifying personal information in your web account file is correct and up to date by contacting our support attendants via our support desk at support@FreeMoneySystem.co.

10.   Internet based data transfer

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore by browsing this Site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this manner.

11.   Changes to this Statement

The owners and publishers of the Site have the discretion to periodically update this Privacy Policy Statement. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy statement and any updates.

12.   Contact us

If you have questions regarding the security of the Site, our Privacy Policy Statement, its implementation, and/or our information collection and dissemination practices, please contact us via our support desk at support@FreeMoneySystem.co.

"Endorsed by ScamWatchdog.org" 

'FreeMoneySystem' © 2015 All rights reserved
